<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="no"?>
<!DOCTYPE business:PatentDocumentAndRelated SYSTEM "/DTDS/ExternalStandards/ipphdb-entities.dtd"[]>
<business:PatentDocumentAndRelated xmlns:base="http://www.sipo.gov.cn/XMLSchema/base" xmlns:business="http://www.sipo.gov.cn/XMLSchema/business" xmlns:m="http://www.w3.org/1998/Math/MathML" xmlns:tbl="http://oasis-open.org/specs/soextblx" xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:schemaLocation="http://www.sipo.gov.cn/XMLSchema/business /DTDS/PatentDocument/Elements/OtherElements.xsd" xsdVersion="V2.2.1" file="GB101998002013003GB00000024948330AFULEN20130320GB00Q.XML" dateProduced="20160726" status="C" lang="en" country="GB" docNumber="2494833" kind="A" datePublication="20130320">
  <business:Claims id="claims01" lang="en" status="C" dataFormat="original" sourceDB="GB">
    <business:Claim id="c-en-0001" num="0001"> &lt;claim-text&gt;-17 -CLAIMS1. A window regulator comprising: a carrier plate for holding a window glass, a guide rail for movably guiding the carrier plate, an orientation changing member provided at. upper end and/or lower end of the guide rail, an inner cable wound around the orientation changing member and connected to the carrier plate, and a drive unit for moving the inner cable in an axial direction of the guide rail, wherein the drive unit has a drum for winding the inner cable, the inner cable is installed substantially linearly between the orientation changing member and the drum, an outer tube is provided in a longitudinal direction outside the inner cable installed substantially linearly, and the outer tube is held by an outer tube holder such that at least an end of the outer tube at the side of the drum is able to swing to follow the swing of the inner cable due to winding and unwinding by the drum.&lt;/claim-text&gt;</business:Claim>
    <business:Claim id="c-en-0002" num="0002"> &lt;claim-text&gt;2. The window regulator of claim 1, wherein the outer tube holder holds the vicinity of an end of the outer tube at the side of orientation changing member.&lt;/claim-text&gt;</business:Claim>
    <business:Claim id="c-en-0003" num="0003"> &lt;claim-text&gt;3. The window regulator of claim 1 or 2, wherein the drive unit is mounted between the upper end and the lower end of the guide rail.-18 - 4. The window regulator of any one of claims 1 to 3, wherein the inner cable up to the vicinity of the drum is protected by the outer tube, and the inner cable from the vicinity of the drum to a position where the inner cable conies into contact with the drum is protected by a drum cover for covering the drum so as to enable the drum to wind and unwind the inner cable.&lt;/claim-text&gt;</business:Claim>
  </business:Claims>
</business:PatentDocumentAndRelated>